This is a real story about my senpai's encounter with her boyfriend.
これは先輩の友達の彼氏が実際に遭遇したっていう話です
It was on a hot, humid, summer day when her boyfriend went by a lonely park.
ある蒸し暑い夏の夜
その彼氏さんが 人気がない公園を通り掛かったの時こと
A woman who happened to be standing
there asked him how to get to the station.
一人佇んでいた女の人に 駅までの道を聞かれたんです
As her boyfriend kindly gave the woman directions,
その彼氏さんが　快く道順を説明していると
the somewhat pale woman slowly raised her hand...
どこかうつらなその女の人が
ふわっと　手を上げて
...and suddenly, in a flash...
突然  ガバーと
In a flash...
ガバーと
Took her blouse off!
ブラウスを脱いだんです
Um...
Hey! That wasn't scary at all!
って　全然まったく怖くないじゃん
放て！心に刻んだ夢を
未来さえ置き去りにして
限界など知らない　意味無い！
この能力が光散らす　その先に遥かな想いを
チカラ
歩いてきた　この道を　振り返ることしか
出来ないなら…今ここで全てを壊せる
暗闇に堕ちる街並み
人はどこまで立ち向かえるの？
加速するその痛みから
誰かをきっと守れるよ
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
身体中を　光の速さで　駆け巡った　確かな予感
掴め！望むものなら残さず　輝ける自分らしさで
信じてるよ　あの日の誓いを
この瞳に光る涙　それさえも強さになるから
Even if we try hard to make the atmosphere scary,
せっかく雰囲気を作っても　そんな話ではね
it's useless if it's that kind of story
えぇ  　実際遭遇したら怖くないですか
Come on... If you actually encountered her, wouldn't you be scared?
An urban legend about a woman who suddenly undresses... "The Undressing Woman"!
いきなり抜き出し都市伝説「脱ぎ女」
Not scary at all!
怖くない
Wouldn't she just be considered a
pervert instead of an urban legend?
と言うより　それで　ただの変質者じゃないの
Well then... How about a tale like this?
じゃあ　じゃあ　こんな話はどうですか
Hmm?
うん
When the wind turbine propellers start turning the other way,
風力発電のプロぺラが逆回転するとき　町に異変が起きる
something strange happens to the city!
At 4:44PM, you shouldn't cross between school district boundaries!
夕方四時四十四分に　学区を跨いではいけない
Otherwise you will wander into the legendary "Imaginary Number School District".
幻の虚数学区に迷い込む
An item that increases your ability just by using it: the Level-Upper!
<Level Upper>
使うだけで能力が上がる道具　幻想御手
そんなくだらないサイト見るのはお止しなさいな
Quit looking at childish sites like that.
Urban legends are so un-scientific.
大体　都市伝説なんて　非科学的な話
ここは天下の学園都市よ
We're in the famous Academy City, you know.
Oh, have a little adventurous spirit!
もう 　浪漫がないな
There are also cases where real things become rumors, too.
それに　本当に起きた出来事が形を変えて噂になっている場合もあるですから
Like a guy who has an ability that prevents other abilities from working on him!
「どんな能力も効かない能力」を持つ男の人っとか
Doesn't that sound Academy City specific?
学院都市ならではって感じじゃないですか
どんな能力も効かない能力？
An ability that prevents other abilities from working?
Nonsense! There's no way an ability like that exists.
そんなむちゃくちゃな能力あるわけないですわ
Right, Onee-sama?
ね　お姉様
Uh...
Yeah, that's right.
そうね　本当にいるなら一度戦って見たいわね
If he really exists, then I'd like to try fighting against him.
Well, only if he actually exists.
まあ　本当にいればね
Magazine: Real Academy City Urban Legends
都市伝説ね
Urban legends, huh?
A guy who has an ability that prevents other abilities from working on him.
「どんな能力も効かない能力を持つ男」なんて
Yeah right.
Hey, you're cute.
君可愛いね　お
Oh, and you're from Tokiwadai!
しかも　常盤台じゃん
今から俺たちと遊びに行かない
How about you go out with us for a bit?
Don't worry, we'll make sure you get home.
帰りは送ってやるから
We don't know how late it'll be, though.
まあ　いつ帰れるか分かんねけど
-Idiots. Trying to hit on me...
-Don't worry, you'll be home by the morning after the next day.
私に声をかけてくるなんて馬鹿な連中ね
-It's not that they're cold-hearted.
別に 彼らが薄情ってわけじゃない　分かってる
Let's go.
I know.
Even if they got involved in this, they
wouldn't be able to do anything, anyway.
実際ここに割って入って来ても
何かできるわけじゃないし
怪我をするだけだ
They would only get themselves hurt.
-What are you looking at?
-Everybody likes themselves.
誰だって自分が可愛い　それが普通
That's normal.
見ず知らずの人間のためにそんなことするやつがいたとしたら
If there is someone who would help some complete stranger,
そいつはただの馬鹿か
that person is simply an idiot, or...
Oh, there you are!
あ　いた　いた
Looks like my companion caused you trouble.
やぁ　連れがお世話になりました
Man, you shouldn't just go off on your own!
駄目だろう　勝手に逸れちゃ
Bye guys!
じゃあ　どうも　あははは
Who are you?
誰　あんた
Huh?
へ？
うまく合わせろよ
Hey, just go along with the script!
My "Pretend to be an Acquaintance and Naturally Pull Her Out of the Messy Situation" plan is ruined!
知り合いの振りして「自然にこの場から連れ出す」作戦が台無しだろう
Why must we do something so troublesome like that?
何でそんな面倒くさいことしなきゃならないんのよ
Who do you think you are?
何だ　てめえ
You made a fool out of us.
なめた真似しやがって
You got something against us, huh?
なんか文句でもあるのか
えっと
Too bad, then.
しょうがないな
Huh?
Yeah, I do.
あ　そうだよ  恥ずかしくねえのか　お前ら
Don't you feel embarrassed?
All of you gather up and circle around a single girl.
こんな大勢で女の子一人を囲んで情けない
大体　お前らが声掛けた相手をよく見てみろよ
Just look at the person you tried to hit on.
-Oh wow.
まだガキじゃないか
She's just a kid!
ガ…
先あい取り見ただろう
You heard that conversation, didn't you?
年上に敬意を払わないがさつな態度
She has a rude attitude and has no respect for her elders!
ガ…
She might look like an ojou-sama, but she's still acting like some teenage rebel!
見た目はお嬢様でも
まだ反抗期も脱げてねえじゃん
She's just a little kid!
そんなガキだぞ
Guys like you who can't deal with a little kid without ganging up annoy me!
俺はな　お前らみたいに群なきゃガキも相手にできないのやつら
むかつくんだよ
The type of person that makes me the most annoyed,
私が一番むかつくんのは　お前だ
is you!
Heh...
Huh?
Why didn't my electric shock work on him?
何であいつには私の電撃が効かないの
Could he really be like that guy in the urban legend?
まさか　本当に都市伝説通り
ありえない　　私が本気出せばあんなやつ…
That's impossible!
If I get serious, he'll just be...
今度あったら絶対に
The next time I see him, I'll definitely...
ええと　目印とか何か覚えてないんですか
Um, do you remember any landmarks that might help?
Landmarks. Hmm...
目印か
Oh, there was a crosswalk right in front.
目の前に横断歩道があったな
Crosswalks aren't good landmarks...
横断歩道じゃ　あんまり目印とは
あんた
Hey, you!
Oh, it's the Biribiri middle schooler!
お  　びりびり中学生
I'm not Biribiri!
びりびりじゃない　御坂美琴
I'm Misaka Mikoto!
Today will be the day we put an end to all this!
今日という今日は決着つけてやるんだから
So that means you have some free time now.
ってことは　お前今暇なんだなぁ
I have all the time in the world to waste!
時間なら　たっぷりあるわ
じゃこの人の駐車場を探すの　手伝ってくれんない
Will you help me find this person's parking lot then?
はあ
Huh?
Well, I forgot where the parking lot I parked my car was.
いや
車を泊まった駐車場がどこだか分からなくなってしまってね
Oh, hey... Why?
えっ　ちょっと　何で
俺　行かなきゃならないとこがあってさ
Well, I have to go somewhere.
You're free, so it's fine, right?
お前暇なんだから　いいだろ
It's not a matter of whether it'll be fine or not!
いいだろじゃねえっつの
I won't let you blow me off with some random excuse again!
また適当にあしらおうだってそうは行かないわよう
毎回毎回のらりくらり適当なことばっか言って
You make up all this crap every time we meet!
-It's just really hot.
いや　それにしても暑いな
Real-
W-What are you doing?
何　何をしているんですか
炎天下の中　ずいぶん歩いたからね
I've been walking in the sun a lot, so I'm sweaty.
汗びっしょりだ
何をこの人
Who is this person?!
I just met her a while ago, myself!
俺も先知り合ったばかりだし
J-Just put your shirt back on! Please!
とにかく　シャツを着てください
Oh my, a woman's being attacked!
あ 　女の人が襲われている
Did that guy force her clothes off?
あの男の人を脱がしたの
そうじゃない
That must be it!
ち 違う　誤解だあ
T-That's wrong...
You've all got the wrong idea!
H-Hey!
ちょっと
君　シャツを持って行かれるのはなら困るんだが
Hey, you. I'll be in trouble if you take my shirt away.
Oh my.
Just put your clothes on! Please!
と　とにかく　服を着てください
Everyone's watching!
見られてます　見られてますから
Everyone is watching, so please hurry!
ほら　速く
ここは涼しくて　生き返るな
This place is cool and refreshing.
What's with her?
なんなの　あの人
She suddenly takes her shirt off in public.
人前で突然服を脱ぎだして
Oh...
Come on. If you actually encountered her, wouldn't it be scary?
えっ 　実際遭遇したら怖くないですか
An urban legend about a woman who suddenly undresses... "The Undressing Woman"!
いきなり抜き出す都市伝説「脱ぎ女」ってないない
Oh, that's impossible.
もしもし　お姉様　今どちらですの？
Hello?
Onee-sama, where are you?
これから初春たちとお茶しに行くのですけれど　一緒にいかがです
We're going to have tea with Uiharu and Saten.
Do you want to join us?
Well, you see, I'm with some weird person right now...
それが　なんか変な人と一緒でさ
"Weird," you say?
変　とは？
She suddenly took her shirt off?
突然服を脱ぎ出した？
Oh, that must be "The Undressing Woman"!
それで　きっと「脱ぎ女」ですよ
Are you okay, Misaka-san?
大丈夫ですか御坂さん
ちょっと　おやめなさいあなた達
放して　放してください
Hey, stop it you two!
Oh, take a picture and email it to me!
後　シャメ　シャメをお願いします
Hey, now-
Don't start thinking it's funny and try to compare it to some urban legend.
あのね　　面白がって都市伝説に繋がらないでよ
ちょっと変わってるけど　普通の人間
She's a little awkward, but she's a normal person-
変わっているというのは　私のことかなぁ
Are you talking about me being awkward?
Oh, suddenly asking a stranger... and... well... you know...
いいえ　そんな　見も知らぬ人を捕まえて　ねぇ
The number you have called is unavailable.
おかけになった電話は現在繋ぎすることができません
-She switched it to voice mail.
留守電
Is she in trouble?
やばいんじゃないんですか
We might want to go look for her.
探しに行ったほうが良いんじゃないですか
Only idiots are serious about urban legends.
都市伝説本気にするなんて　大馬鹿さんですわよ
Huh?
付き合ってもらう　お礼だ
It's a thank you present for helping out.
Oh, thank you.
あ　いただきます
Hot.
Why hot?
何で　ホット
And... curry soup?
しかも　スープカレーって
When you're hot, you should drink warm drinks.
暑いときには暖かいの飲み物のほうがいいのだよ
それに　カレーのスパイスには疲労回復を促すものが含まれてる
Plus, the spices in the curry help you feel refreshed.
Well, I might understand the logic,
まあ　理屈は分かる気もしますが
but my feelings are telling me that I want a cold drink.
気分的には冷たいもののほうがいいな　なんて
Feelings...
気分か　若い娘さんはそう言う選択の仕方をするものだったな
But yes, young girls make choices that way.
I'll go buy something new.
買えなおそう　何がいい？
What do you want?
いいです　いいです　お気持ちだけで十分です
Oh, don't worry about me!
It's the thought that counts.
I'm sorry. I'm doing so much research that my brain tends to think in too logically.
すまないね
研究ばかりしてるせいか　理論的に考える癖がついてるものてな
Research... So, you're a researcher?
研究って　学者さんなんですか？
Cerebral physiology. I mainly do
research on AIM dispersion fields.
大脳生理学　主に「AIM拡散力場」の研究してるんだ
You mean the weak power that ability users emit unconsciously?
それで　能力者が無自覚に周囲に発散している微弱な力のことですよね
Yeah. So you learned about it in school already?
ああ　もう授業で習ったかい？
Yes, in my first year.
え　一年の時に
I heard it was such a weak power it's not detectable by human sensory organs, and it can only measured by machines.
人間の五感では感じ取れず
機械を使わなければ計測できないぐらいの弱い力だって
私はその力を応用する研究をしてるんだ
I do research on applications of that power.
Oh, really?
え　ってことは　能力についてもお詳しいんですか
So, does that mean that you know a lot about abilities?
Is there something you want to know about?
何か知りたいことでも
Well...
えっと
Um... Is there an ability that cancels out other abilities?
その「どんな能力も効かない能力」なんてあるんでしょうか
Well, there are many abilities out there.
能力と言ってもいろいろあるからな
What kind of abilities won't work, for example?
たとえば　どんな力を効かないんだ
Like having no problem surviving high level electric shocks.
高レベルの電撃受けてもなんともなかったり
Electric shocks, huh?
電撃か
For example, an ability that produces something like a lightning rod that averts the electric current.
たとえば避雷針のようなものを発生させ 電流を逸らせるような能力とか
そういうものとはまた違う感じなんですけど
It's different from that, though...
それは君の知り合いか
Do you personally know this person?
Eh?
えっ？
いいえ　都市伝説ですよ　都市伝説
Oh, no... It's just an urban legend, you see.
I just happened to hear about it.
ちょっと小耳に挟んだもので
Urban legends, huh?
都市伝説か　最近の若い子でもそういう話をするのか
So young girls these days talk about that stuff, too.
Well, it's not so much that they're popular, but that we have a lot of them.
まあ　流行ってというか　いろいろあるんですよ
Like "The Undressing Woman".
「脱ぎ女」とか
"Undressing Woman"?
脱ぎ女？
Ah, it's nothing!
いや　いいんです　別に
Oh!
Hmm?
ご　ごめんなさい
I-I'm sorry!
Oh, don't worry about it.
気にすることはない
It'll be fine if I wash it quickly.
すぐに洗えば大丈夫だ
I told you not to undress!
だから　脱ぐなって
#4 Urban Legends
A Certain Scientific Railgun
都
市
传
说
Huh?
はぁ？
Onee-sama still won't pick up.
お姉様　まだ繋がらない
"The Undressing Woman" must be attacking her!
「脱ぎ女」に襲われてるんですよ
Quit that foolish talk.
だから　そんな酔った話を
佐天さん「脱ぎ女」の情報がたくさん書かれたサイト見つけましたよ
Saten-san, I've found a website with lots of
information about "The Undressing Woman".
Let me see.
どれどれ
What?!
What's the matter?!
どうしたんです
Shirai-san, the people who meet the Undressing Woman make a final scream and then become unresponsive.
白井さん　「脱ぎ女」に遭遇した人は
叫び声を最後に残して　連絡が取れなくなるって
Oh, you're making up stuff again.
またそんなこと
Onee-sama is the strongest. The invincible Electroshock Princess of Tokiwadai.
大体お姉様は　常盤台中学が誇る
最強無敵の電撃姫なのですよ
There's no way some "Undressing Woman" who just undresses will beat her.
そんなただ脱ぐだけの「脱ぎ女」にやられるなんてありえませんわ
Wrong. Something even scarier might be happening.
いいえ　もっと恐ろしいことが起きているかも
What do you mean?
どういう意味ですの
The undressing is infectious!
「脱ぎ女」って伝染するって
It's infectious?!
伝染って
Those who have come in contact with "The Undressing Woman" also become "Undressing Women" because of her curse!
「脱ぎ女」にあった人がその呪いで　自らも「脱ぎ女」になるって
Oh my!
えっ？　それじゃ　御坂さんもあっちこっちで服を
That means Misaka-san will be going around flashing herself!
No way!
そんな　まさか　お姉様
Onee-sama, you can't!
あははは
No!
Onee-sama!
いや　お姉様　お止めになって
Don't do it anymore!
Shi-Shirai-san?
白井さん
Uiharu! Find a way to undo the curse!
初春　呪いを解く方法見つけなさい　すぐに
Immediately!
Oh, please don't be so serious about it!
そ　そんな　本気にならないでください
That's right. It's just an urban legend!
そうですよ　ただの都市伝説ですよ
Sorry to trouble you.
面倒掛けて申し訳ないね
Well, I can't just quit midway.
まあ　乗り掛かった船ですよ
Here you are.
どうぞ
Thank you.
ありがとう
Oh, yes. Please remember to thank that guy.
そうそう　あの彼にもお礼を言っといてくれ
That guy?
彼
He's your acquaintance, right?
知り合いなのだろ
Right when I was in trouble, he called out to me.
途方にくれていた私に声を掛けてくれたのだよ
Oh, did he?
へぇ～　あいつが
He's a good guy.
いい子だな
He just meddles in other people's affairs, like a wanna-be cool guy.
お節介なだけですよ　格好付けって言うか
He talks to you, throws you at someone else, and disappears.
大体声を掛けておいて　人に押し付けて姿くらませるなんて
How irresponsible of him.
無責任ですよ
How should I say it...
なんていうか
Either he's good at dealing with people,
人をあしらうのがうまいって言うか　適当って言うか
he just isn't serious, or...
いろいろむかつくんですよ　いつだって自分が
he does a lot of things that annoy me.
It's like he's always-
楽しそうだな
Looks like you're having fun.
え
What are you...
You like him?
君は　あれか　彼が好きなのか
何を
W-What are you...
Well, they do say that people sometimes treat the one they love coldly.
ほら　好きな相手には冷たくしてしまうと言う昔流行った
It was popular a while ago. What was it? Tsun... Tsun...
つん　つん　つんだら　いや　つんじるか？
Tsundara?
No...
Tsunjire?
That's impossible!
ありえないから
What's wrong?
どうした　何があった
What happened?
I wonder?
何でしょうね　ささ　行きましょう
Now, now. Lets' hurry.
Thanks a lot.
いろいろとありがとう　それじゃ
All right then.
Take care.
お気をつけて
Rather...
つうか　自分の車泊めた駐車場分からなくなるって　どうよ
How could she forget which parking lot she parked her car in?
Geez.
まったく　何で私がこんなに疲れなきゃならんないのよう
Why am I so tired?
It's all his fault.
全てはあいつのせいだ　今度あったら絶対に
If I meet him again, I'll definitely...
Argh!
きゃぁ
It's completely totaled!
全滅だ　重要な蛋白源が
My precious source of proteins!
I-I waited in line for two hours just for this!
せっかく　せっかく　二時間も並んだのに
あ！
Oh.
Thanks for leaving me and running off like that!
先はよくも私を置いて逃げったわね
You leave the troublesome work for others and go shopping?
人に厄介こと押し付けておいて自分はお買い物か
For poor students, it's a matter of life and death whether or not you can get the special, on-sale items!
貧乏学生にっとて
特売品の手にいられるかどうかは死活問題なんだ
常盤台のお嬢様にはわかるまい
An ojou-sama from Tokiwadai wouldn't understand this!
I had lots of trouble too!
こっちだって大変だったんだから
汚れたスカート脱ぎだすわ
She started taking off her dirty skirt,
しょうがないから　洗って上げるわ
and I had to wash it since there was no other choice.
So in the end...
あげくの果てにはつん…
Tsunde-
Tsun?
つん？
A-Anyway, fight me! Just fight me!
と　とにかく　勝負しなさい　勝負
"Fight me," you say?
勝負　勝負って
But you've lost every match.
今までのお前の全戦全敗じゃんか
Shut up!
煩い　私だって　一発も食らってないだから　負けてないはよ
I haven't been hit a single time, either.
I haven't lost!
じゃあ　どうしたら　終わるんだよ
Then how do we finish this?
Well...
それが　もちろん　私が勝ったらよ
Of course, after I win!
は
You! Don't sigh even more loudly than before!
そこ　先より大きいため息つかない
All right.
分かったよ
If that's what will make you happy...
それで気が済むてんなら　相手になってやる
...then I'll be your opponent.
So you're finally getting serious.
やっとその気になったわね
We won't cause any trouble to the surroundings if we do it here.
ここなら周りに迷惑かかんねえだろう
いつでもいいぜえ　かかって来な
You're free to start any time.
Bring it.
You don't have to tell me!
言われなくても　こちはずっとこんな時を　待ってたんだから
I've been waiting for this chance!
Just as I thought, electric shocks don't work.
やっば電撃は効かないか
Then...
なら
Hey... What?
あ　何
H-Hey, don't use weapons!
ちょっと　お前　得物を使うのはずるいじゃない
I made it using my ability.
能力で作った物だもん
The iron sand is vibrating like a chainsaw.
砂鉄が振動してチェーンソーみたいになってるから
If you touch it, you might bleed a little bit!
くれるとちょっと血が出たりするかもね
Err... I don't think the injuries will be that minor!
どう考えでもそれじゃ済まないと思うんですけど
Even if you dodge my attacks like that, I can do stuff like this, too!
ちょこまか逃げ回ったって
こいつには　こんなこともできるんだから
The sword extended!
剣が伸び
It'll hit!
捕まった　かわせるタイミングじゃ
He can't avoid!
He forced it back into iron sand.
強制的に砂鉄に戻された
But I've expected everything until now.
でも　ここまでは　予想通り
L-Looks like you lose.
勝負あった見たいだなぁ
Really?
さあ　それはどうかしら
Hey, you're even using the iron sand taken by the wind!
お前　風に乗った砂鉄まで
No matter how many times you do this, the result will still be the same!
こんなこと　何度やだって同じ結果じゃないか
Even if you can counter the electric shocks I shoot-
取った　飛んでくる電撃は打ち消せても
The electric current isn't flowing through?
電流が流れて行かない
What is he?
何なのよ　こういつ
Umm...
Well...
え  ええど　やぁ
Gyaaaa!
I-I lose!
ま　参りました
D-D-D-D-D-Don't joke with me!
ふ ふ ふ  　ふざけんなぁ
Fight me seriously!
真面目にやなさいよ
だってお前　びびってんじやん
But you were scared!
I'm not scared at all!
びびってなんかないわよ
Don't lie!
嘘付け
You were like this, in tears, and tiny from curling up!
こんなふうに涙目になって　びっくうってしてから
Die!
死ね
や  ははは
Don't escape!
逃げんな
Hey, you!
お前って　今の直撃してたら普通死ぬぞ
If that actually hit me I would be dead for sure!
It won't affect you anyway!
どうせ効かないでしょうか
It's not a matter of whether or not it works on me!
効こうか効くまいか
How could you use an attack like that on someone without hesitation?
そんな攻撃を重々なんか仕掛けるって
どういう神経だ
I've never used something like that on anyone else before!
私だって　今まで人に向けてこんな能力使ったことはないわよ
Why only me then?
何で　俺だけ
Fight me properly!
ちゃんと私の相手しろう
Ow, hot!
Heh...
I'm home.
はぁ　ただいま
Huh?
あれ　黒子いないのか
Kuroko isn't in?
I'm so tired.
はぁ　疲れた
Onee-sama...
お姉様
Kuroko?
黒子　あんたどこに
Where are you-
You suddenly took off your clothes.
いきなり服を脱ぎ出すなんて
やはり「脱ぎ女」に呪われているですね
That means you must've been cursed by "The Undressing Woman"!
さ　お姉様も　お被にやさませ
Now please put this on your head too, Onee-sama!
なんなの　あんた
What's gotten into you?
This is the only way to undo "The Undressing Woman's" curse!
「脱ぎ女」の呪いを解くためにはこうするしかないのです
Disappear, "Undressing Woman"!
逃げろう　「脱ぎ女」
Quit it already!
やめろうっつの
脱ぎ出せた　脱ぎ出せた
It's still warm!
It's...
So she's the rumored level 5.
<Level 5>
あれが噂の超能力者か
She's an interesting girl.
面白い子だったな
Dear My Friend Every day & night
Always be with you
Dear My Friend every day & night
話しても　まだまだ　足りないまま
夕焼けが　街を染めてゆく
思うように　なかなか　いかない…って
気づいたら　一緒に　泣いていた
恋も　夢も　花も　虹も　風も
ぜんぶ掴もうよ
ダイジョウブ！　元気出して
私がそばにいるから
今日のミス　悔やむより　今　乗り越えて
ダイジョウブ！　迷わないで
まだ見ぬ未来へと向かって
ずっと　歩いてゆこう
Dear My Friend every day & night
Always be with you
Next Episode
Hey, I really had a lot of fun today.
やぁ　今日は楽しかった
A Certain
Newbie Training
of Two
某
二
人
的
新
人
研
修
この上予告を任せてもらえるとは
And they even let me do the preview!
ここはひとつ華麗に脱いで決めるとしよう
I should expose myself splendidly to show off, then.
さて　次回
So next episode-
脱ぐなぁ
Don't undress!